

Personnal skills

- ✓ Strong interpersonal skills
- √ Teamworker
- ✓ Flexible and creative
- ✓ Efficient problem solver
- √ Project management
- √ Highly organised
- \checkmark Outstanding attention-to-detail

Tech Skills

- √ Object-Oriented programming
- ✓ Parsing and scaping data
- ✓ MVC (Model View Controller)
- √ Schema Design & SQL
- ✓ DB & ActiveRecord

Programming Languages

- \checkmark HTML5, CSS3 , Javascript ES6
- √ Ruby on Rails

Languages

- √ French : Native
- √ English: Fluent
- ✓ Spanish: Intermediate

Tools

- √ Visual Studio Code
- √ Bootstrap
- √ JavaScript Tools (Webpack, yarn)
- √ GitHub
- √ Slack
- √ Figma

Artistic skills

- √ Hand drawn art
- √ Tatoo design
- ✓ Mural mandal wall @poartry.by.pauline

LET'S CHAT



0919-484-064



Taipei, Taiwan



<u>paulinerouge@hotmail.com</u>



<u>paulinerouger</u>



paulinetw

Pauline Rouger

Full Stack Developer

HERE'S MY STORY:

Highly motivated Junior Developer seeking for a new professional adventure. I am a critical thinker with strong problem-solving skills with over 15 years' work experience in hospitality/travel industry. I am a fast learner and very adaptable, continually maintaining a positive attitude while interacting with my peers. I am constantly motivated to develop my skills and grow professionally: I am now looking to bring my upbeat and energetic personality as a team member and expand my knowledge in the industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Founder & Travel Planner

2019 - 2021

TIME TO TRAVEL | SINGAPORE

As a self-starter, I take proud to set myself challenging goals and self-motivate to success. Thanks to Time to Travel, I particularly developed my creativity and ingenuity; I developed my business idea and implemented it by participating in the development of my website, by searching for the right management and technical tools, and business strategies. This entrepreneurial adventure in Tourism in the wake of Covid, made me humble and resilient in the face of obstacles.

Team Leader & Senior consultant

2011-2020

HELLOWORLD | MELBOURNE & SINGAPORE

Managing a team of 25 people from 10+ nationalities, deepened my open-mindedness and improved my leadership skills. I learnt to communicate effectively and to be emotionally aware to better meet my team members' concerns. I collaborated proactively across all the group departments.

Restaurant Manager

WIRED CAFE | SAN DIEGO, USA PRIMADONNA | MONTREAL, CANADA 2007- 2010 2004- 2015

Hospitality management takes dedication and hardwork in a fast-paced environment. I flourished in my roles thanks to my efficiency and organisational skills. My ability to multi-task and general adaptability were also keys of my outstanding performance.

Reservation Agent

2005-2017

PARTIR PAS CHER | ANGERS, FRANCE

Specialising in customer service, I would get out of my way to meet customers needs and solve complex situations. I built a strong relationship with my clients which helped the company to establish its customers` loyalty. Always taking the initiative to support struggling team members strengthened my ability to work in team.

EDUCATIONAL INFO

Full-stack Web Developer bootcamp

2021

LE WAGON, MELBOURNE (REMOTELY)

From the database to the user interface, learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

Management Tourism Industry Bachelor

2005

UNIVERSITY OF QUEBEC IN MONTREAL